masbee.com 2011-11-01

# 

**Privacy Policy**

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Masbee Services respects the privacy of your information. Our Privacy Policy governs our online information practices and reflects our commitment to protect your privacy. 

**Security Measures**

Your account information and profile are password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. 

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Masbee Services is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We attempt to keep this information, apart from whatever information is used to market your company to potential trading partners and other related customers. Masbee Services does reserve the right to cooperate with law enforcement inquires and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights when, in its sole discretion, it believes in good faith such information is required to assist such parties. 

**Public Access to Information  
**  
The information you provide will be made available to all users of our website. Please remember that any information you disclose becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personally-identifying information. 

**Disclosure of Information**

We reserve the right to disclose your information where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing (or threatening to infringe) or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our title, rights, interests or property or those of other website users or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

We also reserve the rights to disclose, without notice to you, personal information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority. 

**Co-Branded Relationships**

We have established relationships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services which we ourselves do not offer. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our website, or through offering "co-branded" sites in which both ourselves and these other parties share the same URL, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. The Privacy Policy of such other parties may differ from ours. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding of any offers, products or services provided by such other parties. 

**Cookies**

Masbee Services may set and access cookies on your computer.   
Masbee Services allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Masbee Services's cookies.   
Masbee Services uses web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Masbee Services products and services. 

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to obtain metrics, analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Masbee Services may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

**Spam Protection Policy**

Masbee Services strictly adher to the international Spam Protection polcies and guidelines. We do not sell or rent your personal information to any third party in any form what so ever to protect you from such Spams that occur from time to time. 

Masbee Services also makes sure to restrict the registered to Users to adher strictly to Anti Spam rules while communication inside the network and will take necessary and stren action against such users found guilty of violating such international guidelines and best practices. www.masbee.com platform will have to utilized for the purpose of business and promotional communication between the users (buyers and supplier) only.
